Ângelo Ocanã Martins

Address: K2H 7A9 Nepean, ON E-mail: angeloocana@gmail.com

Phone: (613) 720-9572 Site: angeloocana.com

Github: github.com/angeloocana Pluralsight: pluralsight.com/profile/ocanaangelo

Objective

Senior Nodejs Full-stack Developer (React, GraphQL and MongoDB).

About Me

My professional journey started when I was 14 years-old. Since then, I have been passionate about programming. Most recently, I have my mindset on TDD, Functional Programming, Offline First, Mobile First and Frog Cloud.

I'm an Arch Linux user.

Work Experience

2007 - Present Freelancer Senior Full-stack Developer | Lastest Projects:

- angeloocana.com
 Design and Coding | React, Graphgl and Nodejs
- github.com/polutz/polutz
 Coding | React, Graphql, Nodejs and Docker
- <u>novoterritorio.azurewebsites.net</u>
 Coding | Angular, Ionic, C#, MongoDB and MS Azure
- staffgeist.com
 Coding | Angular, Ionic, C#, MongoDB and MS Azure
- jumpoverjump.com
 Design and Coding | Angular, Ionic, C#, MongoDB and MS Azure
- angeloocana.com.br
 Design and Coding | Angular, Ionic, C#, and MS Azure

2011 - 2015 POL, Peela, Total On Demand

Lead Senior C# Software Developer

- Developed web platform for Small-Medium marketing and endomarketing campaigns, 5-8 projects every year. 5K-9M Users.
- Provided consultations to extract clients needs and develop strategies,
- Created their own e-commerce platform.

Technologies: C#, .net MVC, web forms, sql server, DDD, Lucene and Amazon AWS.

Clients: Loreal, Johnson, Sony, Vivo|Telefonica, Volkswagen, Walmart, BASF, Net, FMC, FTD, Sky, OI, BRF, Syngenta, Cury, Tenda, B2W, Magazine Luiza, Casas Bahia, FastShop, ...et al.

2010 -2011 Empresário Cobrança

Lead C# Software Developer

- Developed web platform to manage debt collection.
- Worked with complex math algorithms to calculate interest rates.
- Created company's own barcode generation software.
- Development of internal Human Resources systems.
- Building access control system using web cams.
- Developed an internal financial control system.
- Wrote performative queries to work with a 500GB SQL Server database over millions of rows.

Technologies: C#, WCF, WPF, WebForms, Windows Forms, Windows Services, EXT.Net, SQL Server.

2010 -2010 Media W

C# Software Developer

Developed POS Desktop Terminal following government regulations.

Technologies: C#, Windows Forms and MySQL

2008 - 2010 Upgrade Consultoria

Junior C# Software Developer

- PriManager Developing web platform to manage large-scale construction environments.
- FDE Web platform for managing public schools in São Paulo/BR.
- Developed their own ERP & CRM.

Technologies: C#, Webforms, Telerik, Web Services, Windows Services, Flash / Action Script and SQL Server

Education

2012 - Present	Pluralsight

Design and Technology

pluralsight.com/profile/ocanaangelo

2013 – 2014 UNIP - Universidade Paulista

Analysis and System Development

2011 - 2010 FIAP - Faculdade de Informática e Administração Paulista

Analysis and System Development

2007 - 2009 FIEB

Web Design with Emphasis on Digital Media

Languages

English	Portuguese	French	Spanish
Fluent	Native	Basic	Proficient